Narrator: 1
M: São Paulo is currently the fourth biggest city in the world in terms of population.
Narrator: 2
M: The further south you travel from São Paulo,
the more you notice the German influence in Brazil.
Narrator: 3
M: There is a popular cliché that São Paulo is Brazil’s New York,
whereas Rio de Janeiro is Los Angeles.
Narrator: 4
M: The cost of living in São Paulo is almost twice as high as that of Cairo.
Narrator: 5
F: Unlike some capital cities, Cairo has an extremely efficient metro system.
Narrator: 6
F: Alexandria, Egypt’s second city, is significantly smaller than Cairo.
Narrator: 7
F: Cairo is far and away the most popular tourist destination in Egypt.